Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
Memorabilia Collection
1775-2010
1866-1997
University Archives
Princeton University. Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections
Princeton University. Library. Special Collections
AC053
227 boxes
21 items
This collection contains over 1,800 items including mugs, pipes, canes, banners, hatbands, pins, jewelry, and other material collected by many individuals that document reunions, sporting events, student traditions, and other aspects of University life.
Scope and Contents
The Memorabilia Collection has been rehoused, and the finding aid is in the process of being updated during August and September, 2021. As of August 6, box numbers in Series 6, 7, and 12 are not correct, and not all existing items have been incorporated into the finding aid yet.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by broad category as follows: 250th Anniversary; Awards; Banners, Pennants, and Flags; Clothing; Dishware; Embossers; Grounds and Buildings; Medals; Pins and Ribbons; Athletic Equipment and Ephemera; Stamps, Paper and Desk Accessories; and Smoking Accessories.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was donated by hundreds of individuals over the course of several decades. Some individual items are marked with accession numbers which provide donor information.
Appraisal
No appraisal information is available.
College students -- New Jersey -- Princeton -- Societies and clubs.; Princeton (N.J.) -- Social life and customs.; Collectibles.; Ephemera.; Memorabilia.; Princeton university
- Series 1: 250th Anniversary, 1996-1997; 4 boxes
  Conditions Governing Access
  Collection is open for research use.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains memorabilia related to Princeton University's 250th Anniversary celebration.
  - Postcard, 1996; 1 item (Box 126)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    AR.1996.097
    Blue folder of US Postal post card for Alexander Hall. Sept 20, 1996
  - Medallion, 1996; 1 item (Box 126)
    "Princeton University 250th Anniversary Nassau Hall 1746-1996" on front with picture of Nassau Hall.
  - Pin, 1996; 3 items (Box 126)
    250th symbol.
  - Pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 126)
    "ONE" with U. seal.
  - Pin, 1996; 1 item (Box 126)
    Picture of Alexander Hall postcard.
  - Plaque, 1996 September 20; 1 item (Box 126)
    Plaque with 1996 post card and 1946 Nassau Hall stamp. "Presented to Hal Shapiro, 9/20/96."
  - Paperweight, 1996; 1 item (Box 126)
    Lucite paperweight with invitation inside. Invitation for the "Joint Commemorative Session of the Legislature"
  - Water bottle, 1996; 1 item (Box 127)
    Mineral Water."BCQH2O" 1 liter bottle.
  - Water bottle, 1996; 1 item (Box 127)
    Mineral water bottle. "BCQ H20" 16 oz.
  - Large bowl, 1996; 1 item (Box 127)
    AR.2003.034
    Large commemorative bowl with Princeton shield at bottom. Orange and gold trim with pictures of important buildings on campus around the outside.
  - Umbrella, 1997; 1 item (Box 132)
    Black and orange. 250th celebration.
  - Framed picture of Alexander Hall postcard, 1996; 1 item (Box 141)
    Framed, with postcard and expanded picture of Alexander Hall.
- Series 2: Awards, 1871 June 27-2005 April 7; 29 boxes
  This series contains various types of awards given at Princeton University, and has sub-categories for athletic awards and awards for alumni, as well as other types of ceremonial honors.
  - Alumni, 1871-2000; 19 items
    Awards given to alumni, primarily at reunions.
    - Plaque, 1941-1942; 1 item (Box 58)
      Princeton University Fund Graduate Council Award for the Largest Amount Raised, 1941-1942. Given to the Class of 1909
      AR.2004.037
    - University seal, 1941; 1 item (Box 85)
      Wooden with metal seal. "Grad Council Award, 1940-41 class of 1898 donors 100%."
    - Cup, 1913; 1 item (Box 94)
      Pewter. "Class 1903 Princeton University Decennial Reunion."
      EX4762
    - Goblet, 1914; 1 item (Box 94)
      Class of 1911 3rd reunion, longest distance award.
    - Plaque, Undated; 1 item (Box 173)
      Reunion Long-Distance Prize. Wooden plaque given to member of Class of 1938 who traveled the furthest to reunions.
      AR.2009.040
    - Silver plate, Undated; 1 item (Box 174)
      Class of 1938. Distinguished Service Award.
    - Silver cup, Undated; 1 item (Box 205)
      "Presented to Robert Sylvanus Gardner the boy of 64 by his Fathers Class Mates" inscribed.
      Given by Margaret R. Wright
    - Silver cup, Undated; 1 item (Box 205)
      "Presented by the Class of 1871 Princeton College to Henry Cummings Williams Class Boy born Oct. 4, 1873" inscribed.
      Given by M.F. Williams
    - Silver Cup, Undated; 1 item (Box 205)
      "Class of 1915 Princeton Mid-Winter Reunion Long Distance Cup" on front. Names of Winners on back. One handle broken.
    - Silver Cup, 1871 June 27; 1 item (Box 205)
      "College of New Jersey Class of 1861 Presented to the Class Boy, James Wilde, Son of Edward L. Wilde. June 27, 1871" inscribed.
    - Silver Cup, 1908 June 23; 1 item (Box 207)
      "To Russell W. Moore from his friends in the Princeton Club the 23rd of June 1908" inscribed.
      1
    - Silver Cup, Undated; 1 item (Box 208)
      "The names affectionately inscribed on this cup are those of our classmates whose high achievements have added to the renown of Princeton University and brought distinction to the Class of 1915" inscribed as well as many names.
    - Silver tri-handled cup, 1949; 1 item (Box 212)
      "Princeton 1899." "The class of 1899 at its 50th year reunion bequeaths this cup to the class of 1949 to have and to hold in trust for another fifty years and then, present it to the graduating class of 1999."
    - Silver Bowl, Undated; 1 item (Box 214)
      "Class of 1935 Long Distance Award" Names of winners inscribed.
      AR.1995.092
    - Silver plated cup, 1930; 1 item (Box 218)
      "Loving Cup Exercises June 15th Class of 1915 Princeton University Long Distance Trophy." Inscribed with name. John L. Mott won this award in 1925, Mason Olcott in 1930.
      John L. Mott won this award in 1925, Mason Olcott in 1930.
    - Silver cup, 1933; 1 item (Box 219)
      Three Handled Silver Cup. "In behalf of all who drank here from ..." Inscribed on one side. Names on other two sides.
    - Silver Cup, 1904; 1 item (Box 220)
      "1882 William Stewart Tod for twenty years President of Princeton '84: his classmates upon this our twentieth anniversary by this token hold him in loving regard. 1904" More information inside of cup.
    - Silver plated cup, 1907; 1 item (Box 222)
      "To John A. Campbell for thirty years president of the class of 1877, Princeton University." Inscribed.
    - Annual Giving Campaign Award, 1955-1956; 1 item (Box 100)
      Framed note of gratitude to Arthur J. Horton '42 for Annual Giving Campaign 1955-1956
    - Anniversary Campaign Award, 2000; 1 item (Box 116)
      Edward C. Eisenhart '42.
      AR.2003.001
  - Athletic, 1874-1910; 7 items
    Awards given for athletic events.
    - University seal, Undated; 1 item (Box 20)
      Princeton gun club, Harvard match.
      EX4821/1
    - University seal, Undated; 1 item (Box 20)
      Princeton gun club, Yale match.
      EX4821/2
    - Silver plated cup, 1884; 1 item (Box 64)
      PCAA Caledonian Games 1884. 1st prize hammer throw.
      Gift of Mrs. J Russell Craig, 9/3/80
    - Cup, 1910; 1 item (Box 95)
      PUTAA Intercollegiate Relay race Feb 1910.
    - Trophy and pedestal, Undated; 1 item (Box 146)
      Silver trophy. Presented to Princeton Wrestling Team. Wooden pedestal.
      AR.2006.090
    - Silver Cup, 1874 July 15; 1 item (Box 206)
      "Presented by the Class of 77 of Princeton College to John S. Ely of the Freshman Crew In commemoration of their Victory at the College Regatta Saratoga, July 15 1874" inscribed.
      AR.1990.044
    - Silver Cup, 1874 July 15; 1 item (Box 206)
      "Presented by The Class of 77 of Princeton College to John Campbell of the Freshman Crew In commemoration of their Victory at the College Regatta Saratoga July 15, 1874" inscribed.
  - Plaque, 1996 September 18; 1 item (Box 60)
    Truman Scholarship Honor Institution award. Presented to Princeton University.
  - National Historic Landmark dedication, Undated; 1 item (Box 87)
    U.S. Department of the Interior designation of The President's House as a National Historic Landmark.
  - Award, 2005 April 7; 1 item (Box 95)
    Presented to William H. Scheide '36 for generosity involved in establishing the "Scheide Professorship of Music History."
    AR.2005.045
  - Award, 1981-1986; 1 item (Box 145)
    Small bronze tiger statue. Presented to recognize the volunteers and staff of "A Campaign for Princeton, 1981-1986."
    AR.1993.015
  - Silver Thermos, 1903-1933; 1 item (Box 213)
    "Daffodils of Princeton 1903. 'And then my heart with pleasure fills and dances with the daffodils.' Wordsworth." Names of winners inscribed.
    E4761
  - Silver trophy, Undated; 1 item (Box 216)
    "Princeton Upper Class Club Scholarship Trophy." Nassau bell tower on top.
  - Silver Greek style Cup, 1906; 1 item (Box 217)
    "To the Princeton Quadrangle Club" on front. "In Memory of Frederick Henry Cossitt Dec. 11, 1883- July 1, 1906"
    Given by Herbert A. Davis, '49
  - University seal, Undated; 1 item (Box 58)
    Mock leather with stamped seal.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 item (Box 85)
    Metal 6"x 9". Painted
  - University seal, circa 1921-1930; 1 item (Box 85)
    Wooden with metal seal. Varnished.
    Anonymous gift in memory of Charles W Millard, Jr. '26. Received 10/25/89.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 item (Box 85)
    Wooden with metal seal. Painted seal.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 item (Box 92)
    Wooden with metal seal. Large. One duplicate.
    AR.1995 .034
  - Certificate of Appreciation for Walter Phelps "Buzzer" Hall Upon Retirement, 1952; 1 box (Box 198)
    AR.1992.057
    Signed by the presidents of Princeton classes '1913 to '1952.
- Series 3: Banners, Pennants and Flags, 1876-2008; 16 boxes; 22 items
  This series contains banners, pennants, and flags related to various University events and organizations. It includes several flags that went to the moon in 1969 with Charles Conrad.
  - Flag with Princeton shield, Undated; 1 item (Box 62)
    White flag with Princeton Shield. "Princeton University" in black lettering.
  - "48 Anzacs" pennant, 1948; 1 item (Box 62)
    "'48 Anzacs" Orange.
  - 67 pennant, 1967; 1 item (Box 62)
    "67" Orange. 1967?
  - 76 pennants, 1876; 2 items (Box 62)
    76. Two pennants.
  - 1887 strip banner, 1 item (Box 62)
    "87" 18" Orange.
  - University seal, Undated; 1 item (Box 85)
    wooden with metal emblem.
    AR.1996.051
  - Chamber Chorus Glee Club banner, 1980; 1 item (Box 106)
    Princeton University Chamber Chorus, Glee Club 1980. Maroon and white felt banner.
    AR.2003.030
  - "P" flag, Undated; 1 item (Box 121)
    Orange with a black P on a stick.
  - Princeton Shield, Undated; 1 item (Box 121)
    In a black frame.
  - 1891 pennant, 1 item (Box 125)
    91. Black.
  - 1901 pennant, 1 item (Box 125)
    1901 Black.
  - Felt with verse from "Old Nassau", Undated; 1 item (Box 142)
    Orange felt. "Old Nassau" verse written on it.
  - 1888 flag, 1 item (Box 159)
    "88" Orange flag. 6'x8'
  - 1922 banner, 1 item (Box 160)
    "1922" White. 5'X3'.
    AR.1996.093
  - Class of 1916 banner, 1951; 1 item (Box 161)
    "Princeton 1+9+5+1=16" Orange, 3'X5'
  - 1909 banner, 1 item (Box 161)
    "Princeton 1909" 4'x5' Black.
  - 1921 banner, 1 item (Box 161)
    "Princeton 1921" 4'x5' Black.
  - 1916 banner, 1 item (Box 161)
    "Princeton 1916" 6'X3'
  - Princeton 1938 banner, Undated; 1 item (Box 162)
    Black banner with "Princeton 1938" in orange.
    AR.1997.089
  - Banner, 1915; 1 item (Box 162)
    33x69. Felt, black with orange lettering.
    AR.2000.056
  - Banner, 1919; 1 item (Box 162)
    AR.2000.057
  - Banner, 1928; 1 item (Box 162)
    32x72. Felt, black with orange lettering.
    AR.2000.089
  - Football banner, 1926; 1 item (Box 163)
    "1926" with football and scores(P-10; Y-7; P-12; H-0) Orange. 5'x3'
  - Tiger and cub painting on cloth, Undated; 1 item (Box 163)
    Tiger and cub. 2'x4'
  - Princeton 1922 banner, 1 item (Box 163)
    "Princeton 1922" 21"x46"
  - Embroidered tablecloth, Undated; 1 item (Box 163)
    Signatures embroidered with multi-colored thread (friendship bridge cloth).
    Owned by Joseph Maull Carey '16. Given by Charles and Margaret Carey.
  - Embroidered tablecloth, 1896; 1 item (Box 163)
    Signatures embroidered in orange and black thread.
    Given by Mrs. Graham Hunter in 1952.
  - 1928 banner, Undated; 1 item (Box 164)
    8'X2.5' Black, "Princeton" in orange. 1928.
  - 1916 banner, 1 item (Box 164)
    "1916" 5'X3'.
  - Football banner, 1935; 1 item (Box 164)
    23x45. Felt, black with colored footballs representing opponents with game scores.
    AR.2000.058
  - Graduate College Centennial banner, Undated; 1 item (Box 165)
    "The Centennial of the Graduate College." Large white banner.
  - 1907 banner, Undated; 1 item (Box 166)
    "1907." Black banner with orange lettering.
  - Graduate College Centennial banner, 2000 December 13; 1 item (Box 168)
    "The Centennial of the Graduate School." Large white banner.
    AR.2004.012
  - 1904 banner, 1 item (Box 169)
    6ft.x10ft. Orange (cotton?) with "1904" in black.
    AR.2001.057
  - 1899 banner with bird, circa 1899; 1 item (Box 170)
    Large black and white banner with large orange bird and "99"
  - Cloth, Undated; 1 item (Box 171)
    Red oriental run with U seal. 9"x6"
  - Bird on orange felt, Undated; 1 item (Box 171)
    Bird on orange felt. 6"x9" Class year symbol.
  - Tiger skin rug painted on felt, Undated; 1 item (Box 171)
    Painted tiger skin rug on felt. 12"x9"
  - Princeton banner with seal, Undated; 1 item (Box 172)
    17" x 9" "Princeton" and seal in orange. Orange border.
  - Embroidered cloth "P" and seal, Undated; 1 item (Box 172)
    White with orange U seal and "P".
  - Flag, Undated; 1 item (Box 172)
    Orange and black with handle.
  - Paper flags, Undated; 24 items (Box 178)
    Orange paper flags with black lettering "Princeton."
    AR.2008.125
  - Class of 1970 locust flag, Undated; 1 item (Box 178)
    Class of 1970. White flag. Locust with Princeton Shield on its back. With picture of creator.
    AR.2006.005
  - Class of 1879 35th reunion cloth, 1914; 1 item (Box 179)
    Orange, rectangular, 7.5"*21"; 35th reunion of the class of 1879; List of US Presidents, from Washington to Wilson.
  - Football players pennant, Undated; 1 item (Box 179)
    "Princeton" with tiger head and football players' names.
  - Pennant with buttons and pins, Undated; 1 item (Box 179)
    "Princeton" with buttons and pins attached.
  - Scroll painting of tigers and cheetahs, Undated; 1 item (Box 179)
    Tigers and Cheetahs.
  - "P" banner, Undated; 1 item (Box 182)
    15"'X15". Black with orange P
  - Tiger head pennant, Undated; 1 item (Box 182)
    "Princeton" with tiger head. Black and orange.
  - Moon flag with seal, 1969; 1 item (Box 182)
    One of five that were took to moon by Charles Conrad '53 in 1969.
  - Princeton '95 banner, 1895; 1 item (Box 183)
    "Princeton '95" 2'x2' Orange and black.
  - Banner, Undated; 1 item (Box 183)
    Black with orange "Princeton". 18"x30"
  - "CEW" pennant, Undated; 1 item (Box 183)
    Black on one side, orange on other. Rope border. Black "P" on orange pennant on black background. "CEW" on Orange background.
  - Princeton Yale 1897 banner, 1 item (Box 184)
    3'x4' "Princeton Yale May 7, 1897 Winning Team" Black.
    EX4568/4
  - Banner, Undated; 1 item (Box 184)
    Black felt with fringed edges. 2'x2'. "Princeton"
  - F. Earl Christy painting of a woman's face, Undated; 1 item (Box 184)
    University seal with woman's face. By F. Earl Christy. 2'x2'
  - Small cloth with "79", circa 1879; 1 item (Box 185)
    3'x3' cut cloth. "79"
  - Hanging rug, Undated; 1 item (Box 185)
    Princeton pennant with tiger and seal on Turkish rug-type background. 3'x18"
  - Tiger head pennant, Undated; 1 item (Box 185)
    "Princeton" with tiger head. Black.
  - Scroll painting of tiger, Undated; 1 item (Box 185)
    Tiger.
  - "P" banner, Undated; 1 item (Box 186)
    Orange banner with black "P."
    AR.2005.035
  - Gibson girl and football player painting, circa 1900; 1 item (Box 189)
    Picture painted on canvas. Gibson girl holding Princeton pennant and Princeton football player.
  - Flag, Undated; 1 item (Box 190)
    Orange and black bars. 2'X1.5'.
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 item (Box 190)
    Black and orange with "Princeton."
  - Class of 1970 locust banner, Undated; 1 item (Box 193)
    Class of 1970. White field featuring locust with Princeton Shield on its back.
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 item (Box 193)
    Black. Princeton, with U. Seal.
  - 150th Anniversary flag, Undated; 1 item (Box 194)
    Orange. Tiger with firecracker. 1746-1896. Celebrating 150th.
  - "87" pennant, Undated; 1 item (Box 194)
    "87" black and orange.
  - Pennant, Undated; 1 item (Box 194)
  - "76" pennant, circa 1976; 1 item (Box 194)
    "76."
  - Class of 1956 silk cloth, Undated; 1 item (Box 202)
    Black with tigers, etc. Class of 1956.
  - American flag from Blair Arch, 1959; 1 item (Box 203)
    American flag with 49 stars. Flew over Blair Arch.
  - Embroidered framed pennant, Undated; 1 item
    Black and Orange with "Princeton" embroidered. Framed.
  - Moon flag in frame, 1969; 1 item
    Flag in frame. White with orange and black seal. Went to moon. "To Bud with best wishes Charles Conrad P'53 14-24 Nov '69"
  - American flag from Faculty Room, Undated; 1 item (Box 203)
    American flag with 48 stars that hung in the Faculty Room in Nassau Hall.
  - Princeton logo banners, undated; 3 items (Box 172)
    Misc. white banners with Princeton logo (3)
  - Moon flag mounted on cardboard, 1969; 1 item (Box 198)
    Princeton flag that went to the moon. Signed by Charles Conrad.
    AR.2006.027; donation of Larry Stupski '67
  - "Princeton '93" banner, circa 1893; 1 item (Box 199)
    "Princeton '93" on orange and black silk or satin
    AR.1993.005
- Series 4: Clothing, 1878-2010; 52 boxes
  The clothing group includes handkerchiefs, hats and hatbands, neckties, patches, T-shirts, jackets, socks, some swatches of fabric and other small fabric items.
  - Graduation gown fabric swatches, undated; 1 item (Box 178)
    Blue sample PhD graduation gown sample swatches and letter
    AR2003.68, #1734
  - "79" silk cloth, undated; 1 item (Box 125)
    Small orange silk rectangle, "79"
  - 1 iron-on transfer, undated; 1 item (Box 96)
    Iron-on transfer in original packaging
  - Assorted patches, 1942-1979; 5 items (Box 47)
  - Class of 1905 15th reunion hatband, circa 1920; 1 item (Box 75)
    1905. Quindecennial Reunion hatband with pin.
    AR.2009.089, #1787
  - 1905 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    1905. Orange and black hatband.
    AR.2009.089, #1788
  - 1905 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    AR.2009.089, # 1789
  - 1905 hatband, undated; 1 item (Box 75)
    Orange hatband with "05".
    AR.2009.089, #1791
  - Tiger head patch, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    1"x 1".
  - Class of 1985 25th reunion tote bag, 2010; 1 item (Box 143)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. Tote bag with reunions logo.
    AR.2010.132
  - Class of 1975 reunion fabric swatch, circa 2004-2005; 1 item (Box 178)
    Class of 1975. Reunion costume fabric swatch. Orange and black with "'75" logo and tiger.
    AR.2009.114
  - Reunion costume fabric swatch, circa 2004-2005; 1 item (Box 178)
    Reunion costume fabric swatch. White fabric with orange and black stripes.
  - Class of 1969 reunion fabric swatch, circa 2004-2005; 1 item (Box 178)
    Class of 1969. Reunion costume fabric swatch. Orange and black yin yang pattern.
  - Class of 1980 reunion fabric swatch, circa 2004-2005; 1 item (Box 178)
    Class of 1980. Reunion costume fabric swatch. Black fabric with Nassau Hall pattern.
  - Class of 1981 reunion fabric swatch, circa 2004-2005; 1 item (Box 178)
    Class of 1981. Reunion costume fabric swatch. White fabric with black and orange "81" logo.
  - Class of 1995 reunion fabric swatch, 2005; 1 item (Box 178)
    Class of 1995. 10th reunion costume fabric swatch. White and orange striped fabric.
  - "35" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 178)
    Princeton Shield with "35." Possibly class of 1935, or another class' 35th reunion.
    AR.2007.029
  - Princeton flag patch, undated; 1 item (Box 178)
    Patch with Princeton flag embroidery.
    AR.2010.123
  - Class of 2002 patch, circa 2004-2005; 1 item (Box 178)
    Class of 2002. Reunion hat and shirt patches.
  - Class of 1930 patch, undated; 2 items (Box 178)
    Class of 1930. Princeton shield patch with university motto.
  - Princeton Outing Club Patch, undated; 1 item (Box 178)
    Princeton Shield with "P.O.C."
    AR.2004.097
  - Hat, undated; 1 item (Box 19)
    Orange and black hat with black brim.
    AR.2006.086
  - Class of 1985 25th reunion hat, 2010; 1 item (Box 19)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. White baseball hat.
  - USS Princeton hat, undated; 1 item (Box 22)
    Navy blue hat with gold lettering "USS Princeton CG 59."
  - "P" hat, undated; 1 item (Box 22)
    Black cap with orange "P" and small brim.
  - "92" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black and pentagonal, outlined on a seal, with "92" in orange.
  - "94" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Orange and round, with "94," a circle around it in black.
  - "94" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black and square, with "'94" in orange.
  - "96" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black and pentagonal, outlined on a seal, with "96" in orange.
  - "98" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Orange seal, with "98" in black.
  - "01" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Orange and black rendition of a tiger; "'01" on the tiger's side.
  - "04" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Orange and rectangular, "'04" in black; white elastic band.
  - "P 1906" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    White and inverse-T-shaped; "P 1906" in orange and black.
  - "P 07" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    White seal outlined in orange and black; "P," "07" embroidered in black.
  - 1909 patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    White seal outlined in orange and black; "1909" in black.
  - "09" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black and square; "'09," a tiger in orange.
  - "1910" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Princeton seal in orange and black, "1910" in orange.
  - "12" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Orange and round, with a black circle, "12" in black inside.
  - "1915" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black and round, with orange outline, "1915" in orange.
  - "1916" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black with Princeton seal and motto in orange and white, "1916" in white.
  - "22" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black seal with a tiger in orange and white, "22" in countershaded on orange.
  - 1923 patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black with Princeton seal and motto in orange and white, "1923" in white.
  - Fortieth reunion patch, 1963; 1 item (Box 47)
    Orange and round, a tiger on a camel, with a beer mug; "to our Fortieth" in black.
  - 1926 patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Orange and round with black rim; "1926" in black.
  - 1926 patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Black and irregularly shaped; tiger with "1926" on the chest and with a "P" beer mug embroidered in orange and white.
  - 1926 patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    White and round with orange rims; a head of tiger, "Princeton," "1926" in orange and black.
  - 1926 patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)
    Princeton seal and motto, with "1926" embroidered in orange.
  - "27" patch, undated; 1 item (Box 47)